One Pace Premium
Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Let's go! Shining! Running! Forever!
Keep pushing forward!
The bond that joins us will never break
and its light will shine on the end of our dreams.
Wake up! Wake up! Wake up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
Freedom is our only compass we need. -We are best friends-
We'll be the ones to carve out our own route.
We spend all our days moving full speed ahead, -Go east, Go west-
each day brings something new and we leave nothing unfinished.
I'm too excited to wait for morning to come. (I can't wait)
And so we might as well just grab the sun,
And forcefully drag it into the sky! Go!
That's right, we're Shining! Running! Forever!
Weave the fragments of our dreams together!
When they become one, that will be our treasure!
Let's go Shining! Running! Forever!
Keep pushing forward!
The bond that joins us will never break
and its light will shine on the end of our dreams.
Wake up! Wake up! Wake up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
Darkness will consume you, Straw Hat!
I won't lose! I'll find One Piece. I'm gonna be the Pirate King!
Every trial we overcome brings a chance for thrills. (I can't stay)
Tomorrow and each day after will be heated, intense.
A chain of excitements!
That's right! Shining! Running! Forever!
Trust your curiosity, follow your heart
and head for your goal, that's what adventure is all about!
Let's go shining! Running! Forever!
Spread open the chart of your dreams!
There's power hidden in the bond between us,
it'll help us grasp the end of our dreams.
Never! Never! Never! Never stop it!
We are the one! Go ahead!
To Green Bit!
The Adventure in the Land of Dwarves!
Move!
You're in our way!
You...
Bellamy.
Why did you cheer me on?
That was so embarrassing.
I haven't changed a bit.
You've changed, Bellamy.
No, you have changed.
You can now use Haki far greater than anyone can imagine.
Looking down on me...
My pride has been broken to pieces!
Straw Hat!
Straw Hat?!
Time Until Drop Point is Reached
45 Minutes
Return Caesar
Team
I-It's here!
I thought a Fighting Fish would be a fish.
Isn't it a fish?
You can't call that a fish! It's no different from a sea monster!
It's a beast!
The guy said they reinforced the bridge
with iron to protect it from them!
I-It's going to be alright, isn't it?!
This bridge is a piece of crap!
We're gonna be okay.
These guys can take care of them.
You handle it, Warlord!
Nah, I can't fight right now.
Here they come!
Deadly...
Green St-
Another one from the opposite side!
They're gonna crush us!
Mille Fleur...
One Million Flowers
Gigantesco Mano
Gigantic Hand
Spank!
Skull Exploding Grass!
You're doing great!
No, we're not! Can't you see how many there are?!
It's a whole school!
Let's just run! It'll take forever to fight them all!
Nose-ya, uncuff Caesar! I want him to fight too!
What are you talking about?! He'll just fly away!
He wouldn't dare make a move like that.
My heart!
You won't die a peaceful death...
after pushing around a genius scientist like me!
Gastille!
Wow! He's really powerful!
As expected from a criminal with a 300 million belly bounty!
Gastille!
Run through!
Like I said, why aren't you fighting?!
It takes a lot of energy to use my ability.
And I have to be at my best on our way back!
Do you understand?!
I need to keep my strength up as much as possible!
Because our enemy is Doflamingo!
Law... Is he really going to fight against Joker?!
Oh no! What should we do?!
The bridge has collapsed.
On top of that, I can't see the other side clearly because of the fog!
A Fighting Fish is coming from the front!
Damn! I can't let it destroy any more of the bridge!
Roo...
It stopped.
We caught it!
Alright, let's pull it in!
We had a decisive battle today!
Let's eat Fighting Fish stew to boost our energy!
Yeah!
Whose voice is that?
Residents of the island?
I thought it was a deserted island.
Hey! Who is over there on the other side?!
We want to cross the bridge!
Oh no! It's a human!
Hurry up! Run!
Law, you bastard! I'll get even with you, I mean it!
Wow, what a view! What a lovely view!
We should have thought of flying from the beginning.
Oh, you're right!
Cut that crap!
How much gas energy do you think you need to fly 3 people?!
I'm an important hostage for you!
The drag marks from the fish end there.
Nobody is here yet.
These waters are filled with ships that were sunk by Fighting Fish attacks.
What was that just now?
What's that?!
Uninhabited Forest North of Dressrosa
"Green Bit"
A wild forest?!
S-So this is...
Green Bit?
What are those giant plants?!
Hey, Joker, it's me! Come get me!
Don't be in such a rush.
Over there is the arranged drop point, the southeast beach.
We will leave you there at 3 in the afternoon.
Look at the beach on the other side!
Isn't that a Marine warship?!
It got stuck on the island! It's not just beached!
How is that possible?
Those cuts on the plants look fresh.
What?
It seems that ship hasn't been here for too long.
Its body is not as damaged as it should be.
Did they make it through the water filled with the Fighting Fish?
It's only a matter of time before the Navy gets here.
What?! Do they know about the trade?!
I didn't know that!
You stupid scientist, you're too loud!
Hey, I'm a wanted person!
Since my boss, Joker, resigned from the Seven Warlords of the Sea,
I'm not protected under any laws!
If you leave me handcuffed on the island where the Navy is wandering, I'll...
I said "Shh! Be quiet!"
Wait a minute! Joker is just a pirate now too!
You look like you're hiding something.
It's just a coincidence.
How could I manipulate the Navy?
I'm thinking about going to Green Bit.
It's not proper to hand me over here! Abort this mission!
The Navy is my enemy as well
since I'm allied with the Straw Hats.
Don't tell me you set me up!
They'll be here in 15 minutes.
You all need to take up sniping and recon positions and cover me.
They may be hiding. Go check the forest.
If you find something, let me know as soon as possible.
Okay, got it.
Wait a minute!
We didn't expect the Navy to be here so...
Time Remaining Until the Exchange: 14 Minutes
Green Bit Forest
R-Robin!
This forest is dangerous! Wait!
Let's not get separated!
Thank you for being so manly, Usopp.
You're too loud!
Please don't leave me!
Can you walk a little slower?
Ouch! Don't stop so suddenly, Robin...
Who is it?! The Straw Hats?!
We've been found!
Where?! Where are they?!
You're wrong! I'm Leo!
It's the Navy. Who are they talking to?
Looks like they knew we were coming to this island.
Are you good people or bad people?!
We're the Navy! We protect the citizens.
We're definitely good people!
Then hand over your weapons!
We won't give you our weapons! We have a mission!
Show yourself!
Huh?! What's going on?!
I can't see. It's too fast.
What is with this forest?!
Damn it!
We've been stripped of everything!
Mille Fleur...
One Million Flowers
Campo de Flores!
Flower Field
I caught one!
Huh?! What did you catch?!
It looks like a dwarf!
What?!
What's in her bag?
A book, a notebook, and some clothes.
A candy.
A Snail Phone.
Make sure to take all of her weapons.
There's something suspicious under her clothes!
We are searching her clothes!
No abnormalities at Point C.
Roger.
No abnormalities at Point A.
She's not hiding anything around Point B either.
The Big Human has woken up!
Go on the alert!
Okay!
Ow!
Don't try to run! Stay calm!
My body is sewn to the ground!
It's no use trying to move!
With my magic Stitch power,
I've sewn you to the ground.
Stitch power?
That's right! I sewed you up with this needle!
You're a villainous Big Human, aren't you?
I'm sorry, but I think there's been a misunderstanding.
Are you a devil fruit user?
I'm a Tontatta Tribe warrior, Leo!
Tontatta Tribe Member (Dwarf)
Warrior Leo
Leo-san. Where am I?
Where is Usopp?
I mean, the other human, where is he?
Is he okay?
The long-nosed Big Human was also captured in accordance with our kingdom's rules.
So this place is the country of dwarves, isn't it?
Indeed, this is what our tribe has raised, underneath the great forest, the Tontatta Kingdom.
The forest? You mean Green Bit?
Did you people grow all those giant plants?!
Yes! There is no plant that we can't grow!
Watch out, everybody!
Kabu-san!
This Big Human can sprout flower-like hands on the ground!
Flower-like hands?!
We've never grown such things!
Yes, it must be magic! The strangest thing I've ever seen!
There was no time to run before she caught me!
Are you the one who stripped the Navy soldiers of their things?
I got hypnotized by something and they must've carried me here.
I could probably get away from here with my power, but it would only make matters worse.
Big Human! What is your objective?!
Are you here to destroy the Tontatta Kingdom?!
No! I'm sorry! I just caught him out of curiosity.
Whatever the reason is,
we can't let anybody who has seen our Tontatta Tribe live.
No way! I wasn't going to hurt any of your people.
And I'll never tell anyone that I saw you!
Don't lie!
I don't wanna hear your excuses!
I mean it!
What?
In that case, it's okay!
What?!
Oh, what a relief!
I thought she was a bad person.
Great!
They believed me!
They're so trusting...
You're free now!
Here, these are your glasses.
Thank you.
Hey, Leo!
Tonta-chief-sama!
Just what are you doing?
Tonta-chief-sama, she is a good person!
No way!
But she said so herself.
What?!
Okay then.
He also believed it?!
Why are everyone here so trusting?!
Well well, we don't often have a chance to stare at a Big Human like this.
Who are you?
My name is Gancho, the greatest Tonta-chief of Tontatta Kingdom.
Tontatta Tribe Tonta-chief (King)
Gancho
You can stay as long as you like.
Where is my Transponder Snail?
Oh!
I released it into the wild!
Oh no! It's almost three!
I have to call Law!
Where is the exit?
I must go!
Wait! Are you leaving?
You're a good person, aren't you?
If you're a good person, give us a weapon!
That's the rule!
If you don't give us one, we're gonna strip you of all you have!
But I don't have any weapons!
Then we have no choice.
We're gonna strip you of all you have!
Take everything she has!
No! Wait a minute!
What's the matter?
That Big Human is...
the hero's partner!
What?!
T-The hero?!
Usopp?
Who is this hero that you're talking about?
I'm talking about the other Big Human that we captured earlier.
He has appeared for our sake!
He's the legendary... legendary...
He's the legendary hero!
That's good!
Awesome!
I wanna see him!
Usopp... What kind of lie...?
Dressrosa
Harbor City Acacia
Turn right! I said "Right"!
Why did you turn left?!
Shut up! Be quiet! You're distracting me!
Mom, he's talking to himself...
Don't look him in the eye!
I'm in hurry!
Not as much as I am!
If I don't make it, it'll be your fault!
Get to the Flower Field!
All right! Just shut up!
Ow, ow, ow... This is no good!
I'm such a klutz! This human will see me!
I have to run! Otherwise, the human will...
I'm such a klutz!
A klutz and stupid and a fool!
I always knew I'd fail like this!
This is the true identity of fairies.
A toy?
I'm not a toy!
Tontatta Tribe Member (Dwarf)
Scouting Unit: Wicca
I'm Wicca from the Tontatta Tribe!
Please don't tell anybody that you saw me!
What now?!
I can't walk! I think I twisted my ankle earlier!
I'm such a klutz, klutz, klutz!
What's with that power? You're smashing the ground.
Please!
Take me to my commander!
When you come right down to it, it's kind of your fault.
You stole my sword!
We manage the greenery of this land!
The Big Humans of this kingdom call us "fairies" and give us things!
I have to go! I'm a member of a scouting unit!
I have to report the Donquixote Family's whereabouts to my commander!
Now is our chance!
I saw the Donquixote Family on their way to attack the Straw Hats' ship!
What?!
I'm such a klutz! I told him everything!
Hey, is that true?! I'm a member of the Straw Hats!
Klutz! I'm such a klutz! Klutz!
Stop destroying the town!
Calm down, fairy!
Is it true that the Donquixote Family is going to attack the Sunny?!
It's a secret! But I saw it!
Oh, I did it again!
I don't have a Transponder Snail.
There's no way to tell them about it.
Of all the crew,
I can't believe they're attacking those four.
Alright, I'm gonna head back to the Sunny!
Wait!
Take me to the Flower Field first!
I'll guide you to the sea right after that!
No, I'm gonna head to the sea now!
But...
you're running in the opposite direction!
You don't know which way to go, do you?!
So you're saying...
Doflamingo's people were following our movements.
Yes. That is what we had observed.
Do you guys have some kind of a connection with Doflamingo too?
Yes! Oops!
That is a secret.
Damn it! Not only is the ship in danger, but the rest of us as well!
Hey, are we there yet? The Flower Field?!
Go up the stairs there!
I said "Go up"!
Are you a f-fool?
Shut up!
Dressrosa
Corrida Colosseum
Wait! Monkey-san!
I got you!
Like I said! What kind of place is the Flower Field?!
Be quiet and keep running. I'll fill you in later.
Don't let the police see you!
Aren't you a soldier?!
Soldier-san!
Rebecca.
I saw the list in the Colosseum.
I figured you would enter the competition.
I told you not to!
I...
I'll do it! I'll win it!
Soldier-san!
So...
And then... let's live together!
A warrior who cries so easily cannot win a competition!
Hey, hurry up and go!
Huh? You sure?
It's fine.
Quickly, now!
Is it really okay?! That girl was crying!
That's why we must hurry!
I'm just a toy, but I have something that I want to protect!
Though I can't shed tears from these tin eyes.
Green Bit
Southeast Beach
The appointed time for Caesar's hand-over...
is in two minutes.
Hey, Law! This is Sanji!
Black Foot-ya huh? Did you find the factory?
That's not important now!
Listen carefully!
You've got to get out of there!
What are you talking about?
I have to hand Caesar over soon!
Doflamingo never resigned from the Seven Warlords of the Sea!
Even if you give Caesar back to him, the deal is off!
We've been...
totally deceived!
I don't understand...
How...
You have to get off the island, now!
The news about Doflamingo was wrong?
What do you mean by that, Saka-san?
Are you saying the Navy Headquarters were fooled by a false report?
Yea, it's really aggravating.
I'm going to go talk to the Five Elders at Mariejois.
I'm sorry, but that's how it is.
I need you to keep going ahead to
Trafalgar Law and Doflamingo's meeting point.
Roger that.
All units! To the southeastern beach!
Hurry up!
You fool. It's too late.